U.S. Emergency Board No. 142 Records 5059
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Transcripts. Carriers' Exhibits. Union Exhibits. Joint Exhibits. (Box 1)
  - Union Exhibit 41. Captain's gross weight rates. (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Union Exhibit 42. Captain's international override by airline. (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Union Exhibit 43. Captain's operational duty pay by airline. (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Union Exhibit 44. First officer's base or longevity pay by airline and years of service. (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Union Exhibit 45. First officer's percentage of captain's flight pay. (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Union Exhibit 46. First officer's international override by airline. (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Union Exhibit 47. First officer's operational duty pay by airline. (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Union Exhibit 48. Second officer's base or longevity pay by airline and years of service. (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Union Exhibit 49. Second officer's percentage of captain's pay by airline and years of service. (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Union Exhibit 50. Second officer's international override by airline. (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Union Exhibit 51. Second officer's operational duty pay by airline. (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Union Exhibit 52. B-707-131 Comparative rates of compensation. (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Union Exhibit 53. B-720 B Comparative rates of compensation. (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Union Exhibit 54. CV-880 Comparative rates of compensation. (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Union Exhibit 55. L-1049 G Comparative rates of compensation - pilot. (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Union Exhibit 56. L-749/A Comparative rates of compensation - pilot. (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Union Exhibit 57. L-049 Comparative rates of compensation - pilot. (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Union Exhibit 58. B-707-131 Comparative rates of compensation - pilot. (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Union Exhibit 59. B-720 B Comparative rates of compensation - Senior co-pilot. (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Union Exhibit 60. CV-880 Comparative rates of compensation - Senior co-pilot. (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Union Exhibit 61. L-1049 G Comparative rates of compensation - Senior co-pilot. (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Union Exhibit 62. L-749/A Comparative rates of compensation - Senior co-pilot (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Union Exhibit 63. L-049 Comparative rates of compensation - Senior co-pilot. (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Union Exhibit 64. B-707-131 Comparative rates of compensation - Senior second officer. (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Union Exhibit 65. B-720 B Comparative rates of compensation - Senior second officer. (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Union Exhibit 66. Aircraft pegged speeds proposed and present agreements. (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Union Exhibit 67. Captain's longevity pay proposed and present agreements. (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Union Exhibit 68. Captain's hourly pay proposed and present agreements. (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Union Exhibit 69. Captain's mileage pay proposed and present agreements. (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Union Exhibit 70. Captain's gross weight pay proposed and present agreements. (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Union Exhibit 71. Captain's operational duty pay proposed and present agreements. (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Union Exhibit 72. First year salary per month proposed and present agreements. (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Union Exhibit 73. First officer's percentage of Captain's total pay proposed and present agreements by years of service. (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Union Exhibit 74. Second officer's percentage of Captain's total pay proposed and present agreements by years of service. (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Union Exhibit 75. Second officer seniority comparison. (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Union Exhibit 76. B-707-131 Comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Union Exhibit 77. B-720 B. Comparison and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Union Exhibit 78. CV-880 Comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Union Exhibit 79. L-1649 Comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Union Exhibit 80. L-1049 G Comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Union Exhibit 81. L-749 A Comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Union Exhibit 82. B-707-131 First officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Union Exhibit 83. B 720 B First officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - Union Exhibit 84. CV-880 First officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Union Exhibit 85. L-1649 First officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Union Exhibit 86. L-1049 G First officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - Union Exhibit 87. L-749 First officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Union Exhibit 88. B-707-131 Second officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Union Exhibit 89. B-720 B Second officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Union Exhibit 90. CV-880 Second officer comparison of proposed and current yields for various pay hours. (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - Union Exhibit 91. Contractual changes by airline, 1945-1961 (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - Union Exhibit 92. Major airlines completing collective bargaining agreements immediately prior to and following the last Trans World Airline agreement. (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - Union Exhibit 93. B-707-331 Domestic rates of compensation Senior captain - 85 hours, one-half day - one-half night. (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - Union Exhibit 94. B-707-131 Domestic rates of compensation Senior captain - 85 hours, one-half day - one-half night. (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - Union Exhibit 95. CV-880 Domestic rates of compensation Senior captain 35 hours, one-half day - one-half night. (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - Union Exhibit 96. Trans World Airlines rates of compensation. B-707-131 as compared with Eastern Airlines rates of compensation both before and after the signing of the Trans World Airlines agreement. (Box 1, Folder 213)
  - Union Exhibit 97. Graph of Union Exhibit 96 (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - Union Exhibit 98. Trans World Airlines rates of compensation adjusted for changes in the cost-of-living and national productivity with proposed changes in rates of compensation., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 215)
    August 1, 1958
  - Union Exhibit 99. Extract from civil Aeronautics Manual 40 "Scheduled interstate air carrier certification and operation rules." (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - Union Exhibit 100. Trans World Airlines condensed timetable. (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - Union Exhibit 101. Trans World Airlines Eastbound international schedules. (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - Union Exhibit 102. System operations bulletin. (Box 1, Folder 219)
  - Union Exhibit 103. Domestic flight crew assignments., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 220)
    October 29, 1961.
  - Union Exhibit 104. Extract from Civil Aeronautics Manual 41, certification and operation rules for scheduled air carrier operations outside the continental limits of the United States. (Box 1, Folder 221)
  - Union Exhibit 105. Flight assignments - international pilots. (Box 1, Folder 222)
  - Union Exhibit 106. Trans World Airlines pilots seniority list., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 223)
    July 1, 1961
  - Union Exhibit 107. Flight crew domicile list., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 224)
    November 1, 1961.
  - Union Exhibit 108. Deadhead time. (Box 1, Folder 225)
  - Union Exhibit 109. Comparison - deadhead pay and credit. (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - Union Exhibit 110. Compensation. (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - Union Exhibit 111. Miscellaneous pay rules. (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - Union Exhibit 112. Pay and credit when a supervisor is assigned to a pilot's scheduled trip. (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - Union Exhibit 113. Trip and training expenses. (Box 1, Folder 230)
  - Union Exhibit 114. Article about increased federal expense allowances. (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - Union Exhibit 115. 75 cents per hour expense justification breakdown of average daily costs. (Box 1, Folder 232)
  - Union Exhibit 116. Comparison of expense sections. (Box 1, Folder 233)
  - Union Exhibit 117. Agreement amendments. (Box 1, Folder 234)
  - Union Exhibit 118. Retirement - outline of pilots' proposals. (Box 1, Folder 235)
  - Union Exhibit 119. Vesting for retirement purposes. (Box 1, Folder 236)
  - Union Exhibit 120. Retirement - early retirement benefits. (Box 1, Folder 237)
  - Union Exhibit 121. Table of disability benefits. (Box 1, Folder 238)
  - Union Exhibit 122. Interest guarantees for pilot contributions to fixed benefit plans. (Box 1, Folder 239)
  - Union Exhibit 123. Required company contributions to pilot variable annuity plans. (Box 1, Folder 240)
  - Union Exhibit 124. Insurance - outline of pilots' proposals. (Box 1, Folder 241)
  - Union Exhibit 125. Insurance. (Box 1, Folder 242)
  - Union Exhibit 126. Physical examinations. (Box 1, Folder 243)
  - Union Exhibit 127. Physical examinations. (Box 1, Folder 244)
  - Union Exhibit 128. Vacations. (Box 1, Folder 245)
  - Union Exhibit 129. Vacation comparison - hours free of duty prior to start of vacation. (Box 1, Folder 246)
  - Union Exhibit 130. Hours of service - outline of pilots' proposals. (Box 1, Folder 247)
  - Union Exhibit 131. Comparison of scheduled flight time limitations - single crew operation. (Box 1, Folder 248)
  - Union Exhibit 132. Scheduled duty aloft. (Box 1, Folder 249)
  - Union Exhibit 133. Eastern - working rules and limitations. (Box 1, Folder 250)
  - Union Exhibit 134. Effect of improved trip and duty formulae - piston equipment - domestic system. (Box 1, Folder 251)
  - Union Exhibit 135. Hours of service. (Box 1, Folder 252)
  - Union Exhibit 136. Excerpt from opinion of chairman of board of arbitration, Case A - 6008, Arbitration 252, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 253)
    In the matter of a dispute between Trans World Airlines, Incorporated and the Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association, International. June 30, 1960.
  - Union Exhibit 137. Hours of service comparison. (Box 1, Folder 254)
  - Union Exhibit 138. Comparison of scheduled block-to-block speeds. (Box 1, Folder 255)
  - Union Exhibit 139. Productivity comparison. (Box 1, Folder 256)
  - Union Exhibit 140. all multiple service configurations. (Box 1, Folder 257)
  - Union Exhibit 141. Productivity comparison - Boeing intercontinental super jet - piston Jetstream trans-Atlantic flights. (Box 1, Folder 258)
  - Union Exhibit 142. Productivity comparison - Turbojet (707-331) and piston (L-1649 A) equipment, current international schedules. (Box 1, Folder 259)
  - Union Exhibit 143. Comparison - Domicile staffing. (Box 1, Folder 260)
  - Union Exhibit 143. Bed pilots versus regular reserve pilots. (Box 1, Folder 261)
  - Union Exhibit 144. Comparison of number of pilots., 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 262)
    January 1, 1958 and November 1, 1961.
  - Union Exhibit 145. Productivity comparison - effect of replacing piston equipment with short-range turbo jet equipment on currently operated domestic passenger schedules. (Box 1, Folder 263)
  - Union Exhibit 146. Productivity comparison - effect of replacing piston equipment with long and medium-range turbo jet equipment on currently operated domestic passenger schedules. (Box 1, Folder 264)
  - Union Exhibit 147. Productivity comparison - pilot crew requirements. (Box 1, Folder 265)
  - Union Exhibit 148. Pilots' crew requirements - Trans World Airlines system. (Box 1, Folder 266)
  - Union Exhibit 149. Pilot crew requirements - Trans World Airlines system formula bid pilots added by pilots' proposal. (Box 1, Folder 267)
  - Union Exhibit 150. Pilot crew requirements - Trans World Airlines system comparison of current agreement - pilots' proposals - company's proposals. (Box 1, Folder 268)
  - Union Exhibit 151. Years of service Trans World Airlines system. (Box 1, Folder 269)
  - Union Exhibit 152. Airline pilot fatigue question. (Box 1, Folder 270)
  - Union Exhibit 153. Stress and fatigue. (Box 1, Folder 271)
  - Union Exhibit 154. Flight fatigue in jet aircraft. (Box 1, Folder 272)
  - Union Exhibit 155. New York Times article: "Body cycle upset by jet-age speed.", 1961 (Box 1, Folder 273)
    November 11, 1961.
  - Union Exhibit 156. New York Times article: "Hazards of jet tourism", 1961 (Box 1, Folder 274)
    November 19, 1961.
  - Union Exhibit 157. Working conditions comparison - piston equipment - turbo-jet equipment. (Box 1, Folder 275)
  - Union Exhibit 158. Flight crew monthly flight time record, Trans World airlines, Incorporated - J.B. Archer (Box 1, Folder 276)
  - Union Exhibit 159. Flight crew monthly flight time record, Trans World Airlines, Incorporated - F.W. Burcham. (Box 1, Folder 277)
  - Union Exhibit 160. Flight crew monthly flight time record for C.O. Johnson - Trans World Airlines (Box 1, Folder 278)
  - Union Exhibit 161. Reserve officer assignments. (Box 1, Folder 279)
  - Union Exhibit 162. Training and route qualification. (Box 1, Folder 280)
  - Union Exhibit 163. Furlough and employment protection - examples of existing agreements comparing pilots' proposal with similar language. (Box 1, Folder 281)
  - Union Exhibit 164. Moving expenses - examples of existing agreements comparing pilots' proposal with similar language. (Box 1, Folder 282)
  - Union Exhibit 165. Moving expenses comparison. (Box 1, Folder 283)
  - Union Exhibit 166. Comparison of length of time a company will pay for moving expenses to a newly established domicile. (Box 1, Folder 284)
  - Union Exhibit 167. Definitions: examples of existing agreements comparing pilots' proposal with similar language. (Box 1, Folder 285)
  - Union Exhibit 168. Effect of pilot proposals on increased formula hours. (Box 1, Folder 286)
  - Joint Exhibit 1. Trans World Airlines senior captain monthly pay Trans World airlines versus Air Line Pilots Association. (Box 1, Folder 287)
  - Joint Exhibit 2. Boeing 707 - 131 domestic rates of compensation senior captain - 85 hours one-half day - one-half night. (Box 1, Folder 288)
  - Joint Exhibit 3 - Boeing 707 - 331, International Rates (Box 1, Folder 289)